{
    "id": "9aead5a068a143f0b92c9230161f67e5",
    "title": "Intransitive phrasal verbs exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "8a162359f07d460a89c4e72b0d376fa8",
            "title": "Intransitive Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The car …………………….. on the way to work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "broke down",
                        "broke off",
                        "broke away"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "All songs in that film are …………………….. with youngsters.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "catching on",
                        "catching up",
                        "catching off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t want to …………………….. here ever again.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "come back",
                        "come in",
                        "come on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The thieves must have …………………….. through the back door.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "come on",
                        "come in",
                        "come up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was hit hard on the head, but …………………….. again after a few minutes.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "came off",
                        "came at",
                        "came to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Julie had promised to …………………….., but she never did.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "come in",
                        "come up",
                        "come over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I absolutely like it when old friends ……………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "drop at",
                        "drop by",
                        "drop off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He earns just enough to ……………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "get by",
                        "get away",
                        "get off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Granny tried to …………………….., but she couldn’t do it on her own.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "get on",
                        "get up",
                        "get to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t want to …………………. to that country ever again.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "go back",
                        "go away",
                        "go in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}